Richmond **Nyame**

Address:

David Friedländer-weg 150, 13057 Berlin

Telephone:

+491588818753

Email:

nyamerichmond100@gmail.com

Date of birth:

04.03.1994

Status:

Single, No children

Profile

I have 1 year of professional experience that I gained while working as a research assistant in a university. I am fluent in English. I am perceived as an energetic and committed person. I am looking for an opportunity where I will use and grow my skills as a software developer.

Professional Experience

09/2017 - 08/2018

Research Assistant at the University of Ghana

- Carried out sediment and grain size analysis.
- Assessment of shoreline changes along sea defence structures using remote sensing technology.
- Researched on standards for oceanographic research work.

06/2016 - 08/2016

Tugboat deck crew at Ghana Ports and Harbours Authority

- Making entries in tugboat logbook.
- Cleaning the interior of tugboats.

Education

10/2019 – 03/2022

Studied water engineering at the Technical University of Berlin

Languages

English – C1 Deutsch – A2

Knowledge & Skills

- Python (Entry level)
- MySQL
- Django (Entry Level)
- Good time management.